restaurantsonthego.com 2004-06-05

# Restaurants on the Go! - we deliver from your favourite retaurants

Privacy Policy

We believe that your personal information deserves protection. While you can visit www.restaurantsonthego.com without registering or providing any personal information, you will need to register if you want to place an order. The personal information requested is necessary to process your order. (As noted in the Legal Statement on the website, except where stated otherwise, the term "Restaurants on the Go" used on this website shall be deemed to include Restaurants on the Go Inc. and its respective affiliates, subsidiaries, successors and assigns.) 

What does ROTG use your personal information for?

  * To build your account with ROTG
  * To process your orders
  * To personalize the delivery of content to you

ROTG may also use personal account information and data collected through your personal identification to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use and for sharing with affiliates, subsidiaries, licensees, successors and advertisers. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any personally identifiable information. Your identity is kept anonymous. 

How does ROTG protect your personal information? 

When you provide us with personal information or place an order, it's done through a secure server. One of today's most advanced security systems -- Secure Socket Layers (SSL) -- encrypts all information you provide before sending it to our own server. Only when it reaches the ROTG servers is your information decrypted. 

Does ROTG use "Cookies"? 

Depending on how you have configured your browser, when you shop at www.restaurantsonthego.com, a small file -- a "cookie" -- is stored on your computer. The cookie contains a unique personal identification code and is used to:   

  * save your Shopping Cart and retrieve it the next time you visit the site.
  * personalize your experience by alerting you to features and information we think would interest you.

If you arrive on www.restaurantsonthego.com with your Cookies turned off, you won't be identified until you register and sign-in. 

Does ROTG disclose personal customer information to anyone other than ROTG?

Users' non-aggregated specific personal information is not currently sold, rented or made available to anyone other than ROTG, but we may decide to do so in the future. If this were to happen, ROTG would announce such a plan and ask you to "opt in". By default, we'd assume that you don't want in -- if you wanted to share your personal information, you would have to respond. In the absence of such a response, your information would not be shared with anyone other than ROTG. 

ROTG reserves the right to co-operate with local, provincial and national officials in any investigation requiring either personal information -- including any personal information provided online through www.restaurantsonthego.com \-- or reports about lawful or unlawful user activities on the Web Site. 

ROTG reser ves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We also reserve the right at any time to disclose any information in an individual's account: 

  1. to satisfy any law, regulation or government request;
  2. if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to site operation; or
  3. to protect the rights or property of Restaurants on the Go and its users, sponsors, providers, licensors or merchants.

Contacting us Regarding Privacy

Should you have any concerns regarding privacy on our site or should you wish to have your personal information deleted, please send a detailed description to [info@restaurantsonthego.com](mailto:info@restaurantsonthego.com) so we may address your concerns.
